Okay, in the last video we made some
changes here um where we talked about
where we wrote a multiply function. As
soon as I hit save, this little one
popped up on this little branch. This is
our source control. We're not going to
use Visual Studio source control, but it
does show us that there was a change.
Navigating back to GitHub Desktop shows
us that some things have changed. In
fact, it says someone created a
multiply.js file and they added a line
of code to it. So, what you want to do
is if you want this to be permanent,
right now you've made this change, but
Git isn't tracking it. Um, so you can
make a lot of changes and Git won't
track them until you tell it to track
them. When you tell it to track them,
this is called committing. Um, and
usually there's a couple stages in this
process, but GitHub Desktop simplifies
it for us. So, what you want to do is
you want to give it uh you want to tell
people what change you made. So I'm
going to say created a multiply function
and then I'm going to give it a
description. And this description will
describe what the function does. Um so
I'm going to say um
takes two numbers and multiplies them.
This is a great place to describe why
you made the changes. This one is less
limited on characters than this original
thing. So once you're done, you'll hit
commit. And you'll know you've hit
commit because it'll come back to this
nice blank screen and it says that there
are no local changes. What that means is
everything that you've written locally
has been saved locally to your Git. Um,
but if you want to put it out to the
cloud and onto GitHub, you'll have to
take another